Amar Badnjević



amarba.dev@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/amar-badnjevic

Summary

Graduated from Pan-European university Apeiron in 2021 with a Bachelor degree of Computer Science and Informatics in the field of software engineering (240 ECTS). I have a work experience in Web development, System administration, Devops and IT support. My area of expertise is software engineering and I focus on delivering quality products to clients.

Experience

Backend Engineer, Cloud Services

Klika

Nov 2022 - Present (9 months)

Working on the development of client based projects as well as internal company projects with a strong focus on understanding the business and delivering quality solutions for ease of use.

Software Engineer

Idea4 Infotec Imširović

Jul 2022 - Sep 2022 (3 months)

- Developing web applications using following stack: Django Python PostgreSQL Nginx
- Planning and developing system architectures
- App deployment and management over OVH and AWS services.

System Administrator

asioso

Apr 2022 - Jun 2022 (3 months)

- Installing, configuring and managing Linux servers and Docker containers.
- Maintaining VPN infrastracture

Lead System Administrator

Planet soft

Apr 2021 - Apr 2022 (1 year 1 month)

Managing server and network infrastructure.

Managing Domain, Active Directory, DNS, Office365 administration, etc.

Managing Windows virtual machines through Hyper-V.

Managing Linux virtual machines, their network, application availability, etc.

Configuring and managing main backup system of the company.

Taking care of security using Cisco ASA and Fortinet Fortigate firewall.

Writing and keeping up to date server and network documentation.

IT Support Technician

Pan-European University APEIRON

Feb 2020 - Apr 2021 (1 year 3 months)

Managing hadware and software on desktop PCs for other departments. Monitoring and managing network and server infrastructure, mostly on a physical layer. Visiting departments in other cities for routine checkups and upgrades.

Education

Pan-European University APEIRON – for Multidiscipline and Virtual Studies Bachelor of Computer Science & Information Technologies, Computer Software Engineering

Oct 2017 - Dec 2021

Machine technician for computer design - JU MSS "Sanski Most", Sanski Most Machine technician, Mechanical Engineering Sep 2013 - May 2017

Licenses & Certifications



Introduction to Windows Server Administration - LANACO

11893-01

Skills

Node.js • Troubleshooting • System Monitoring • Team Leadership • Active Directory • Domain Name System (DNS) • Virtual Private Network (VPN) • Network Security • Cisco ASA • Fortinet